School of the Museum of Fine Arts Bulletin UP118
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of the Museum of Fine Arts Bulletin
1989 -- 1994
1941 -- 1994
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Museum Studies Program
UP118
0.25 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains sporadic annual issues from 1941 to 1994 of the bulletin for the School of the Museum of Fine Arts. It lists courses, degree requirements, and general school information.
- School of the Museum of Fine Arts Bulletin, 1941 -- 1994; 1989 -- 1994; UP118.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains sporadic annual issues from 1941 to 1994 of the bulletin for the School of the Museum of Fine Arts. It lists courses, degree requirements, and general school information.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Boston Museum School of Fine Art, 1941 -- 1943; UP118.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Boston Museum School, 1945 -- 1947; UP118.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Boston Museum School, 1953 -- 1954; UP118.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - The Boston Museum School, 1959 -- 1960; UP118.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - The Boston Museum School, 1960 -- 1961; UP118.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    Supplement
  - School of the Museum of Fine Arts, 1977 -- 1978; UP118.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - School of the Museum of Fine Arts Boston, 1988 -- 1989; UP118.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - School of the Museum of Fine Arts Boston, 1990 -- 1991; UP118.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - School of the Museum of Fine Arts Boston, 1992 -- 1993; UP118.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - School of the Museum of Fine Arts Boston, 1993 -- 1994; UP118.001.001.00010 (Box 1)